(Howard:)Well, based on the fact
that our potential market
(Howard:)is about 70 or 80 guys,
(Howard:)and you want a submarine,
(Howard:)I'd say about a
million dollars a pop.
(Raj:)Well, what if we put out a lite
version for half a million?
(Leonard:)You know,
get the word of mouth going.
(Penny:)Hi. I'm sorry
to bother you guys,
(Penny:)but you've got to come
take your Sheldon back.
(Leonard:)What's he doing
in your apartment?
(Penny:)Well, he was moping down in the
lobby, so I invited him over.
(Penny:)Now I regret it.
(Leonard:)Why do you regret...
Uh, never mind, stupid question.
(Penny:)Look, can't you just let him
play with you until bedtime?
(Leonard:)We're not playing.
(Leonard:)This is real work.
(Howard:)We're going to
be hundred-aires.
(Penny:)Okay. What if I got him
to apologize
(Penny:)and promise to behave?
(Leonard:)Then I guess we would
let him back on the app team,
(Leonard:)and while we're doing that,
you could take an aerial tour
(Leonard:)of L.A. on your flying pig.
(Penny:)Okay. Wait right here.
(Raj:)I'll tell you one thing.
If I get rich enough,
(Raj:)that's the kind of girl I want
to take on a submarine ride.